Broadcast Center Recordings, circa 1980-2017: Finding Aid AC362
University Archives
- Series 8: Broadcast Center Recordings, 2015 October 2-2017 July 20; 228 digital files
  - Families Welcome, 2016 September 3; DUS-Student Organizations; 1 digital file (Item 3399D)
    Speakers:Jill Dolan, Rochelle Calhoun, Aleksandra Czulak '17, Charlie Baker '17, and Vivian Bazarko '17, Calvin Chin, Andrew Sun '17; Details: A welcome for freshmen families with a slideshow and guest speakers including Dean Jill Dolan, Vice President Rochelle Calhoun, and students.; Run Time: 46:44:00
  - SHARE: The Way You Move, 2016 September 10; DUS-Student Organizations; 1 digital file (Item 3400D)
    Details: In this student-written, student-performed production, the characters strive to protect their friends from harm as they navigate problematic situations. Learn to be an effective bystander, and become part of the campus movement to prevent interpersonal violence at Princeton. #RespectMatters; Run Time: 1:23:43
  - Andlinger Center for Energy and the Environment Highlight Seminar Series, 2016 September 12; Princeton University. Andlinger Center For Energy And Environment; 1 digital file (Item 3401D)
    Speakers:Alexander Mitsos; Details: \t\nThe center is most known for its Highlight Seminar Series. Notable experts in energy and environmental issues from all over the world are invited to speak. Most seminars are held on Mondays (unless otherwise noted) from 4:00 p.m. ¿ 5:15 p.m. in the center¿s Maeder Hall. A reception will be provided in the lobby of Maeder Hall immediately following the seminar.; Run Time: 1:04:57
  - Dean's Lecture Series: Peter Eisenman, 2016 September 19; Princeton university. School of architecture; 1 digital file (Item 3402D)
    Speakers:Peter Eisenman; Run Time: 1:36:18
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings, 2016 September 21; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3403D)
    Run Time: 47:59:00
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings, 2016 September 23; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3404D)
    Run Time: 51:30:00
  - Signature Lecture: Border Cantos, 2016 September 27; DOC-Wilson College; 1 digital file (Item 3405D)
    Speakers:Richard Misrach and Guillermo Galindo; Run Time: 1:28:50
  - OIT Voices, 2016 September 29; Princeton University. Office of Information Technology; 1 digital file (Item 3406D)
    Run Time: 1:04:31
  - Synthesia of Law (Day One), 2016 September 29; GER-German; 1 digital file (Item 3407D)
    Run Time: 1:27:31
  - Synthesia of Law (Day Two Morning Panel), 2016 September 30; GER-German; 1 digital file (Item 3408D)
  - Nobel Prize Press Conference, 2016 October 04; 1 digital file (Item 3409D)
    Speakers:Duncan Haldane, Christopher Eisgruber, Daniel Day; Run Time: 30:16:00
  - Career Services Presentation, 2016 October 14; DOC-Office of Dean of College; 1 digital file (Item 3410D)
    Details: Presentation. \How Career Services Assists Students in Defining and Pursuing Their Career and Life Vision.; Run Time: 1:09:24
  - Mol 433 - Recording lectures, 2016 October 20; Princeton University. Department of Molecular Biology; 1 digital file (Item 3411D)
    Speakers:Jane Flint; Run Time: 1:02:34
  - Open Access Panel Discussion, 2016 October 27; LIB-Lewis Library; 1 digital file (Item 3412D)
    Speakers:Eugene Higgins, Clancy Rowley, Matthew Salganik; Details: Faculty Panel: What Open Access Means to Me - the panel will share their perspectives on Open Access and discuss the opportunities and challenges that it is making to their research; Run Time: 1:20:53
  - Human Genome Project/Academic Mini-Reunion 2015, 2015 October 02; VPS-Alumni Educ; 1 digital file (Item 3413D)
    Speakers:Heather Thieringer, Senior Lecturer in Molecular Biology; Details: This lecture is part of weekend long program, an Academic mini-reunion for returning alumni classes. October 2-3, 2015. This lecture being recorded is titled: From the Human Genome Project to Personalized Medicine: An interactive lecture on DNA analysis
  - Princeton Freshman Families Weekend Highlight Reel, 2015 October 10; 1 digital file (Item 3414D)
    Speakers:Senior Assoc Dean Claire Fowler, Lesa Redmond, Sofia Gomez, Sindiso Nyathi, Jill Dolan, President Christopher Eisgruber, VP for Campus Life W. Rochelle Calhoun, Kathleen Deignan, The Rev. Dr. Alison Boden,; Details: President's Assembly/ Liberal Arts Panel Discussion
  - 50 years of the National Endowment for the Humanities, 2015 November 16; HUM-Council of the Humanities; 1 digital file (Item 3415D)
  - Hamilton Colloquium with F. Duncan Haldane, 2016 November 17; Princeton University. Department of Physics; 1 digital file (Item 3416D)
    Speakers:F. Duncan Haldane; Details: The Department of Physics Hamilton Colloquium will feature Princeton's F. Duncan Haldane, winner of the 2016 Nobel Prize in Physics.
  - Opening Lecture with Marika Sarder, 2016 November 19; UAM-Education; 1 digital file (Item 3417D)
    Speakers:Marika Sarder; Details: Opening Lecture for Princeton University Art Museum Fall Lecture Series; Run Time: 0:57:22:06
  - Andlinger Center For Energy and the Environment Hightlight - Steven Cowley, 2016 November 09; Princeton University. Andlinger Center For Energy And Environment; 1 digital file (Item 3418D)
    Speakers:Steven Cowley; Details: Steven Cowley, president of Corpus Christi College, Oxford University, will speak on the topic of ¿Driving Down the Cost and Scale of Fusion Energy¿ as part of the 2016-2017 Highlight Seminar Series at the Andlinger Center for Energy and the Environment at Princeton University.; Run Time: 1:21:12:08
  - Trump and the World: A Roundtable Discussion, 2016 November 28; 1 digital file (Item 3419D)
    Speakers:Jeremy Adelman, HistoryMark Beissinger, PoliticsChristina Davis, PoliticsJulia Elyachar, AnthropologyBernard Haykel, Near Eastern StudiesCarolyn Rouse, AnthropoologyKim Lane Scheppele, SociologyYu Xie, SociologyDeborah Yashar, Politics; Details: Join us as we listen to a panel of Princeton professors weigh in on how a Trump presidency is expected to impact the world.; Run Time: 1:21:15:04
  - CITP/PIIRS GSR Lecture: \Internet Resilience: Analyzing the Systemic Risks of a Digital Future\, 2017 January 30; PII-Prin Inst Intl-Reg Stud; 1 digital file (Item 3420D)
    Speakers:Nick Feamster (COS/CITP), Jennifer Rexford (COS); Details: Wednesday, November 30, 2016 Internet Resilience: Analyzing the Systemic Risks of a Digital Future Nick Feamster, Professor of Computer Science, Acting Director of the Center for Information Technology Policy, Princeton University Jennifer Rexford,Gordon Y.S. Wu Professor of Engineering, Chair of the Computer Science Department, Princeton University 4:30pm, Computer Science Building, Room 104; Run Time: 1:07:22:08
  - Artist Talk: Pat Steir, 2016 October 08; UAM-Public Relations; 1 digital file (Item 3421D)
    Speakers:Pat Steir; Details: Painter Pat Steir will discuss her work, including two major paintings that recently entered the Museum¿s collections and are featured in the contemporary gallery, alongside works from the exhibition A Material Legacy, this fall. Steir has been at the forefront of American painting since the late 1980s when she first experimented with her signature pour painting technique. Now in her fifth decade of artistic practice, her canvases bridge the sensibilities of Eastern philosophy, Abstract Expressionism, and Conceptual art.; Run Time: 0:59:54:04
  - Criminality, Deviance, and Anthropological Diversity, 2016 November 15; PII-Prin Inst Intl-Reg Stud; 1 digital file (Item 3422D)
    Speakers:Riccardo Nicolosi; Run Time: 1:18:06:05
  - Statistics, Machine Learning, and Understanding the 2016 Election, 2016 November 07; APC-Applied and Comp Math; 1 digital file (Item 3423D)
    Speakers:Samuel S.-H. Wang,; Run Time: 1:02:23:02
  - ARC Signature Lecture, 2016 December 01; Princeton university. School of architecture; 1 digital file (Item 3424D)
    Speakers:Florencia Pita, Jackilin Hah Bloom; Run Time: 1:07:04:23
  - PIIRS Director's Book Forum: War and Society, 2016 December 13; PII-Prin Inst Intl-Reg Stud; 1 digital file (Item 3425D)
    Speakers:Miguel Centeno; Run Time: 1:22:47:17
  - Artist Talk: Teresita Fernandez, 2016 October 13; UAM-Public Relations; 1 digital file (Item 3426D)
    Speakers:Teresita Fernandez; Details: Teresita Fern¿ndez, whose Nocturnal (Cinematic Sky) is featured in the special exhibition A Material Legacy, will discuss her work and respond to questions. Fern¿ndez is best known for her prominent public sculptures and unconventional use of materials in works that are inspired by a rethinking of the meaning of landscape and place, as well as by diverse historical and cultural references.; Run Time: 1:11:01:12
  - An Evening with Carmen Carrera, 2016 September 29; 1 digital file (Item 3427D)
    Speakers:Carmen Carrera; Details: Join us for a conversation with trans activist and model Carmen Carrera as she discusses her intersecting identities, activism, and work. When not modeling or filming, Carrera devotes her time speaking at conferences throughout South America and abroad, working with organizations like SUE¿OS LGBT to combat transphobia and discrimination. Her work focuses on, among other things, transgender Latinas, making her work both intersectional and inherently Latina.; Run Time: 1:24:32:06
  - Academic Integrity, 2016 September 10; DUS-Student Organizations; 1 digital file (Item 3428D)
    Details: An interactive series of discussions and presentations covering academic integrity and the Princeton Honor Code. First-year students will reflect on the differences between academic integrity at their various high schools and academic integrity at Princeton. They will learn how to succeed academically, with integrity, as undergraduate scholars. Faculty members, deans, and fellow students will de-mystify the Honor Code, plagiarism, and other issues in academic work. By the end of the program, first-year students will feel empowered to make original contributions in class, and informed about the many resources available to them at Princeton.; Run Time: 1:03:58:13
  - Edge Lecture - Jamelle Bouie, 2016 December 01; DOF-Public Lectures; 1 digital file (Item 3429D)
    Speakers:Jamelle Bouie and Princeton's Sam Wang; Details: Edge Lecture by Slate Political Correspondent Jamelle Bouie, in conversation with Sam Wang.; Run Time: 1:27:39:26
  - Class of 2020 Opening Meeting, 2016 September 03; DOC-Advising; 1 digital file (Item 3430D)
    Speakers:Jill Dolan, Rochelle Calhoun, Janet Rapelye, Jeff Wieser '74, Aleksandra Czulak ¿17, Carolyn Liziewski ¿18; Details: Opening meeting for all first-year students. Remarks will be made by the aforementioned speakers.; Run Time: 0:48:17:18
  - Reflections on Diversity, 2016 September 04; DUS-Student Organizations; 1 digital file (Item 3431D)
    Speakers:Sam Offer; Details: Orientation 2016 Session that focuses on community building, diversity, and and inclusion on Princeton¿s campus. The keynote speaker, Rev. Sam Offer, of Washington Consulting Group, is a nationally-known speaker, consultant, facilitator and trainer on diversity and inclusion, social justice, multiculturalism, religion, leadership, and community development.; Run Time: 1:04:28:04
  - Politics Plenary Sessions (Fall 2016), 2016 October 07; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3432D)
    Speakers:Professors Nolan McCarty and Alisha Holland; Details: Politics juniors are required to attend the Plenary Sessions. We plan to make the recordings available only to the students who will be studying abroad; Run Time: 1:37:54:14
  - Politics Plenary Sessions (Fall 2016), 2016 November 29; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3433D)
    Speakers:Professors Nolan McCarty and Alisha Holland; Details: Politics juniors are required to attend the Plenary Sessions. We plan to make the recordings available only to the students who will be studying abroad.; Run Time: 1:28:45:10
  - Carillon Bell Concert, 2016 July 17; ORL-Music; 1 digital file (Item 3434D)
    Details: Carillon recital featuring duets by Lisa Lonie (University Carillonneur) and Janet Tebbel (Guest Carillonneur); Run Time: 1:08:52:16
  - A Narration Alexander Kluge in Princeton, 2016 October 20; GER-German; 1 digital file (Item 3435D)
    Speakers:Alexander Kluge, Devin Fore, Jamie Rankin, Ben Lerner, Phillip Ekardt; Details: Readings, Lectures, Conversations and New Work in Video and Film by Alexander Kluge
  - PSURE Final Presentations, 2016 August 05; DGS-Diversity Initiatives; 1 digital file (Item 3436D)
    Speakers:Dean Dale Trevino; Dean Julie Yun; Dr. Renita Miller; Neal Whetstone (student); Gabrielle Akcelik (student); Jessica Obie (student); Reuben Perez (student); Samanda Robinson (student); Vanya Reid-Hinkson (student); Joshua Strayhorn (student); Eric Pitty; Details: The Graduate School at Princeton University runs an 8 week intensive summer program for non-PU students interested in applying to graduate programs. Students work closely with Graduate School staff on the Diversity and Inclusion Team, graduate student mentors, and faculty mentors to produce original research over the course of 8 weeks. This event will highlight and showcase the work that the students have completed during their time at Princeton University.; Run Time: N/A Multiple "file"s
  - Architecture Spring 2016 Lecture Series - Sandy Attia, 2016 March 23; Princeton university. School of architecture; 1 digital file (Item 3437D)
    Speakers:Sandy Attia; Details: Sandy Attia speaks at Princeton University\nArchitecture Lecture Series - Spring 2016; Run Time: 1:15:22
  - Aspects of Campus Life, 2016 September 10; DUS-Student Organizations; 1 digital file (Item 3438D)
    Details: Featuring Public Safety, University Health Services, and Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students, this session will discuss the values of our community and highlight how to make safe choices and engage in healthy behaviors.; Run Time: 1:14:59
  - 2016 Humanities Colloquium, 2016 September 12; HUM-Council of the Humanities; 1 digital file (Item 3439D)
    Speakers:Eddie Glaude; Details: Only going to record Keynote speaker which is Eddie Glaude starting at 1:30 pm.\n\nMay want a 2 camera set up - to get back to me.\n\n9/9/2016 spoke with Jeannine she said one camera shoot. Starts at 1:30 goes to 2:45 then there's a break until 3 pm so videographer must be done and out by 3 when they resume. JG; Run Time: 1:17:51
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 9-14-2016, 2016 September 14; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3440D)
    Details: These lectures are held in Icahn 101. Recordings are on Mon/Wed/Fri from 10-10:50am before fall break, and then Mon/Tues/Wed/Thurs/Fri from 10-10:50am after fall break. \n\nPlease let us know ahead of time if the equipment is working properly and if these lectures could be recorded remotely. (Equipment is being checked and addressed this month)\n\n\nCompleted on 9-16-16 -- DE; Run Time: 49:46:00
  - On Remembering Others: Vietnam and the Memory of War, 2016 September 19; HUM-American Studies; 1 digital file (Item 3441D)
    Speakers:Viet Thanh Nguyen; Run Time: 1:01:48
  - Politics Plenary Sessions (Fall 2016), 2016 September 23; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3442D)
    Speakers:Professors Nolan McCarty and Alisha Holland; Details: Politics juniors are required to attend the Plenary Sessions. We plan to make the recordings available only to the students who will be studying abroad.; Run Time: 1:32:52
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 9-26-2016, 2016 September 26; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3443D)
    Details: Lecture recordings for ISC231-232 in the fall term.; Run Time: 53:22:00
  - \tBiodiversity Conservation in the Hyperdiverse, Heterogeneous Forests of the Western Amazon, 2016 September 28; EEB-Graduate; 1 digital file (Item 3444D)
    Speakers:Jacob Socolar; Details: The Final Public Oral examination of Jacob Socolar entitled \Biodiversity Conservation in the Hyperdiverse, Heterogeneous Forests of the Western Amazon\; Run Time: 1:06:49
  - BREXIT: Why and How the United Kingdom Leaves the European Union, 2016 September 30; PII-Prin Inst Intl-Reg Stud; 1 digital file (Item 3445D)
    Speakers:Harold James, Linda Colley, Andrew Moravcsik, R. Daniel Keleman, Kim Lane Scheppele; Details: Panel Discussion; Run Time: 1:57:11
  - Dept. of Physics Hamilton Colloquium with speaker Frans Pretorius, Princeton University, 2016 September 29; Princeton University. Department of Physics; 1 digital file (Item 3446D)
    Speakers:Frans Pretorius; Details: Princeton University professor of physics, Frans Pretorius will be providing the Department of Physics Hamilton Lecture. The talk is usually 45 minutes long and followed by Q&A session.; Run Time: 1:10:27
  - Vision & Motion in Collective Behavior, 2016 October 04; EEB-Graduate; 1 digital file (Item 3447D)
    Speakers:Colin Twomey; Details: The Final Public Oral Examination of Colin Twomey entitled \Vision & Motion in Collective Behavior\; Run Time: 59:37:00
  - Synthesia of Law (Day Three), 2016 October 01; GER-German; 1 digital file (Item 3448D)
    Run Time: 2:04:33
  - Dean's Lecture Series: Ellie Abrons, 2016 October 06; Princeton university. School of architecture; 1 digital file (Item 3449D)
    Speakers:Ellie Abrons; Details: Dean's Lecture Series: Ellie Abrons; Run Time: 59:09:00
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 10 December 2016, 2016 October 12; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3450D)
    Details: Lecture recordings for ISC231-232 in the fall term.; Run Time: 48:03:00
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 10-19-2016, 2016 October 19; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3451D)
    Run Time: 47:37:00
  - Faculty Lecture: Machiavelli's Prince on the Eithics of Power:, 2016 October 14; DOC-Office of Dean of College; 1 digital file (Item 3452D)
    Speakers:Melissa Lane; Details: Full title: \Machiavelli's Prince on the Ethics of Power: Should Rulers Be Bound by Everyday Ethics?\ Melissa Lane, Class of 1943 Professor of Politics and Director of University Center for Human Values; Run Time: 50:55:00
  - Faculty Lecture: \Words and Music: Sense and Sensibility\, 2016 October 14; DOC-Office of Dean of College; 1 digital file (Item 3453D)
    Speakers:Donnacha Dennehy; Details: Donnacha Dennehy, Assistant Professor of Music\n \t\nFaculty Lecture:1 Friday 10:00 - 10:50 a.m. Donnacha Dennehy McCosh Hall, Room 50.; Run Time: 53:11:00
  - CITP Conference: The Internet of Things, 2016 October 21; ITP-Events; 1 digital file (Item 3454D)
    Details: The CITP Conference will include 3 Sessions, each with 4 speakers per panel, seated on a stage. The Moderator of each panel will stand at a podium. The Keynote speaker will speak from the podium .; Run Time: 01:51:29 / 01:08:56 / 01:22:26 / 01:19:13
  - Job Talk - Michael GIBILISCO (FQ), 2016 October 25; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3455D)
    Speakers:Michael GIBILISCO; Details: Faculty candidate's job talk for the Dept of Politics; Run Time: 1:19:01
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 10-26-2016, 2016 October 26; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3456D)
    Run Time: 44:55:00
  - Andlinger Center for Energy and the Environment Highlight Seminar Series, 2016 October 24; Princeton University. Andlinger Center For Energy And Environment; 1 digital file (Item 3457D)
    Speakers:Lee Rybeck Lynd; Details: \t\nThe center is most known for its Highlight Seminar Series. Notable experts in energy and environmental issues from all over the world are invited to speak. Most seminars are held on Mondays (unless otherwise noted) from 4:00 p.m. ¿ 5:15 p.m. in the center¿s Maeder Hall. A reception will be provided in the lobby of Maeder Hall immediately following the seminar.; Run Time: 1:03:58
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 10-28-2016, 2016 October 28; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3458D)
    Run Time: 52:42:00
  - Job Talk - Kris-Stella TRUMP (AP), 2016 November 07; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3459D)
    Speakers:Kris-Stella TRUMP (AP); Details: Faculty candidate's job talk for the Dept of Politics; Run Time: 1:14:47
  - An X-Citing Evening with Legendary X-Men Writer Chris Claremont, 2016 November 07; HUM-American Studies; 1 digital file (Item 3460D)
    Speakers:Chris Claremont; Paul Levitz; introduction by Stacy Wolf; Details: A conversation between Professor Levitz and Mr. Claremont, with introduction by Professor Wolf\n\nhttp://ams.princeton.edu/events; Run Time: 1:34:39
  - Job Talk - Jonathan Mummolo (AP), 2016 November 08; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3461D)
    Speakers:Jonathan Mummolo; Details: Faculty candidate's job talk for the Dept of Politics; Run Time: 1:15:43
  - Job Talk - Andrew GUESS (AP), 2016 November 09; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3462D)
    Speakers:Andrew GUESS; Details: Faculty candidate's job talk for the Dept of Politics; Run Time: 1:18:27
  - East Iran in Antiquity: Silk Road and Central Asia outside the Paradigm of Eurasian Trade, 2016 November 09; MRC-Mossavar-Rahmani Center; 1 digital file (Item 3463D)
    Speakers:Khodadad Rezakhani; Details: Aside from the introducer who needs a lav mic, this will be a single speaker who needs a lav mic. He will likely be sharing slides through the room's flat panel, which can be directly inserted into the video during post-production. This room is seminar-style with people sitting around a table (eating) and around the room's periphery.\n\nhttp://www.princeton.edu/iran/events; Run Time: 1:11:30
  - Stephen Kotkin - Keynote, 2016 November 04; PII-Prin Inst Intl-Reg Stud; 1 digital file (Item 3464D)
    Speakers:Stephen Kotkin; Details: Keynote speaker and lifetime achievement award; Run Time: 11:04
  - Job Talk - Ranjit Lall (IR), 2016 November 14; 1 digital file (Item 3465D)
    Speakers:Ranjit Lall; Details: Faculty candidate's job talk for the Dept of Politics; Run Time: 1:19:30
  - Mol 433 - Recording lectures, 2016 November 15; Princeton University. Department of Molecular Biology; 1 digital file (Item 3466D)
    Speakers:Jane Flint; Details: There are a molecular biology classes that needs to be recorded (Audio and Visual):\n10/20/16: 11am - 12:20pm LTL 005\n11/15/16: 11am - 12:20pm LTL 005; Run Time: 1:22:55
  - Dean's Lecture Series: Frank Barkow, 2016 November 17; Princeton university. School of architecture; 1 digital file (Item 3467D)
    Speakers:Frank Barkow; Details: Dean's Lecture Series: Frank Barkow; Run Time: 1:16:01
  - Artist Talk: Shahzia Sikander, 2016 November 17; UAM-Public Relations; 1 digital file (Item 3468D)
    Speakers:Shahzia Sikander\nJames Steward; Details: To celebrate her major public commissions for Princeton University¿s 20 Washington Road¿the new home for the Economics Department and its many international programs, Shahzia Sikander will discuss her work, followed by an interview with Museum Director James Steward. In her pioneering practice, the Pakistani-American artist takes Indo-Persian miniature painting as a point of departure to examine the forces at stake in contested cultural and political histories.\n\nhttp://artmuseum.princeton.edu/visit/calendar/2016-08/artists-talk-shahzia-sikander; Run Time: 1:16:05
  - The Impact of Lead Exposure on our Students, 2016 November 18; 1 digital file (Item 3469D)
    Details: http://www.ers.princeton.edu/events/ers-events/impact-lead-exposure-our-students-what-can-schools-do-mitigate-problem\n\n \t\nOne day conference with panels and speakers; Run Time: N/A
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 11-21-2016, 2016 November 21; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3470D)
    Run Time: 50:07:00
  - ISC 231-232 Lecture Recordings - 11-22-2016, 2016 November 22; LSI-Undergraduate; 1 digital file (Item 3471D)